Thank you.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
You may be seated.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Viewers all over the world, with God, all things are possible.
What are your challenges?
With God, all things are possible.
The life we live is what ushers us into the name, Jesus.
Tell your neighbour, "The life we live is what ushers us into Jesus' name."
The life I live is what ushers me into Jesus’ name.
You can't just wake up and say, "Jesus, Jesus, Jesus...".
Where are you coming from?
That is the question.
Merry Christmas in advance!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I remember the wonderful message you received last Sunday on how you can manage your life,
what you need to do to talk of salvation.
Here are poor people around you.
The relationship between salvation and how we manage our possessions.
We are about to enter a new year.
The solution you apply now will not be able to solve the challenges tomorrow.
It can only solve the challenges now.
Renewal!
Your way and the manner you live brings about what you are seeing around you.
When you want to pray, you don't know what to ask for, because there are numerous challenges.
Because of broken homes, people cannot come together in the morning to pray in the house.
Like I was saying...
The life we live is what moves us into calling Jesus’ name.
That is, the life in the line of God’s Word.
It is not what I'm doing now that will bring whatever you are going to see.
This has been done before my coming out.
Relationship.
This has been done already - I am only coming here to deliver it.
Not to work.
When you wake up in the morning, you need direction
and the direction only comes from the heart, where God lives.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is where God dwells which you can refer to as your spirit
but when you wake up and there is no direction, you make up direction for yourself.
These are the causes of challenges today – making up direction, self-direction.
God is our Director – the direction and the way is what we need now.
Your challenges – leave them for God; think about God.
Every blessing attracts challenges.
Blessing without challenges – you cannot manage the blessings.
Challenges help us to be strong and preserve us for God.
For this coming year you are about to enter, you need to be renewed.
You have everything you need - renewal is the only thing you don't have.
You say you are poor - I disagree; you are not poor.
You are not poor.
(Amen.)
You say you are poor because you don't know how to exploit the things around you.
There are so much blessings - you are in the midst of blessings.
You are in the midst of money - money is everywhere.
You need to be renewed in your spirit.
For how long shall we continue this...?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We are financially "buoyant" more than spiritual.
We are becoming more prosperous than spiritual.
That is a cause of your complaining.
Even if you have money, that complain will not go, that will not remove your nightmare, isolation or depression.
There are many sicknesses and afflictions for which there is no medicine.
You have money, you go to the doctor for the better treatment,
but there are many afflictions without medicine.
If you say money is the answer - what about afflictions without medicine?
These are curses - only God can remove them.
This new year, your spirit must be renewed.
When your spirit is renewed, you will discover yourself.
It is not your sweat or your labour that brings out that blessing you are talking about.
It is our relationship with God that causes this to happen.
When you are renewed spiritually, it will affect your family and children as well.
Ability to be able to put your challenges behind and meditate on Jesus - this is what you don't have.
Tell your neighbour, "Ability to be able to put your challenges behind and meditate on Jesus -
this is what we all lack."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Look at the Word: "In this world there will be challenges" - He said it.
He said, "Put it behind because I have overcome for you."
But the ability to put it behind...
When you have a headache - ignore that headache and focus on Jesus - that is the ability we need now.
You cannot be meditating on your challenges and on Jesus at the same time.
The ability to be able to put behind our situation.
The situation is there: You have a serious headache but you are more of Jesus - with all your heart you are yearning for Jesus.
Just put that behind you: The ability to be able to do that is what we lack.
It seems that our challenges overcome us.
We want to worship God without challenges.
Ability to put our challenges aside and worship Him - our spirits must be renewed.
To renew our spirits, right now, begin to meditate on the Word -
turn it over and over and over in our hearts.
Meditate on it and turn it over and over.
Turn it over - don't let it go.
Continue to meditate on it.
Before you know it...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are saturated already - before you know it.
You must prosper in your spiritual life first.
Get your spiritual life in order; that is where the power, ability of God lies.
There is nothing you have not enjoyed but the relationship with God, you've not enjoyed properly.
Everything: you enjoyed money, pleasure - but relationship with God in a proper way - you have not.
Why can't you put it before you and let it be your first priority?
There is nothing that can change you and bring what you are looking for.
That proper relationship.
It is time that you should know Him like children know their fathers.
Stop imagining Him: "Jesus said this...".
Somebody will tell you, "Jesus says this...".
You should be able to hear by yourself - it is time to hear this.
The life you live here is the life you are going to meet over there.
Don't let anybody tell you, "Heaven, Heaven...".
How do you live this life?
Heaven is reward.
What are you doing and expect a reward?
The file will be opened to you.
You are planting here - you will reap over there.
What are you planting?
Right now, our spiritual life is the first priority.
The money you are looking for, you can never have enough.
Tell your neighbour, “The wealth, possessions you are looking for, you can never have enough”.
Because we can never have enough, there is an urge to steal, to kill, and to destroy.
The urge - because we never can have enough money, possessions, and other things you are looking for.
It is not possible because there are always people above you.
In the spirit, in your relationship with God, there is a place for you.
There is a place for me, there is a place for you.
God purposely created a space for me, "OK, T.B. Joshua - this is yours. This is what to do".
This was only for me.
You too, you have your own space.
There is not much competition, that would make you to be having a...
... unless you are a "zero" - like at the level many of us are today.
You cannot sense or be filled.
The life we live is what moves us into what?
Jesus' name.
What kind of life are you living?
Jesus' name is not just something you can just come and claim, "Jesus, in Jesus..." - no.
The life you live is what moves you into Jesus’ name.
That is, in line with God’s Word.
It ushers us into calling Jesus.
You believe so much in majority, not God’s authority.
Create time for yourself to meet God.
You must cultivate this habit to meet God.
Talk to Him, even though at the beginning it is like, "whom am I talking to? I don't hear from Him.
It is only me who is talking".
I stop when I want to stop, and not when He wants me to stop.
I can't hear, I don't know whether He hears me.
Everything big starts little.
Yes, it will start like that to show your genuine willingness.
Everything starts outside reality.
But when it starts with truth and faith, you begin to enter reality.
Look at what happened to Peter and Jesus.
Jesus was on the sea; Peter said, "I want to come to You".
Jesus said, "You want to come to Me? OK, come".
Outside reality, he started walking on his own power on the sea.
Jesus was looking at him, "I want to see your genuine willingness. If you are genuine, I will come into the matter".
How do we test genuineness?
We test genuineness through challenges.
If your faith is not tested, it’s not real faith.
Our faith must be tested.
That is why we call it, ‘faith’.
Don’t be like Jesus in your body but in your heart; in our heart, we are like Jesus.
With your track record - it is enough not to be deceived.
You should be able to know what is right and what is wrong, when it comes to the issue of God.
Rise up.
Ask the Holy Spirit of Truth to reveal Jesus to you.
The Spirit of Truth, Holy Spirit, reveal Jesus to me!
This is Spirit prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The Spirit of Truth, Holy Spirit, reveal Jesus to me!
Ask Him to help cleanse all your wrongs.
Help cleanse all my wrongs in action, thoughts and deeds – knowingly and unknowingly.
Open your lips, help cleanse all my wrongs.
... you cannot mention.
Viewers, ask the Holy Spirit to reveal Jesus to you.
Make my heart a contact point.
Holy Spirit, reveal Jesus to me.
Do the introduction, Holy Spirit!
Do the engagement, Holy Spirit!
Align me, Holy Spirit!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Cleanse all my wrongs in action, thoughts and deeds – knowingly and unknowingly.
Make it happen, in Jesus’ name!
(Amen.)
Open your lips, pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Pray the character...
Viewers, pray the character of the Holy Spirit into your life.
Be the Spirit of adoption to me, Lord!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In Jesus Christ’s name, we pray.
(Amen.)
Make it happen, in the name of Jesus!
You have so many talents.
Many of us here know that they have talents.
You have gifts.
Being very intelligent but nothing...
Your time seems to be a waste, anywhere you go.
Some talents are dormant.
Nobody calls for your talent, nobody asks of you.
Many are working under those who are dormant and can't offer anything.
It is your talent they are using, but you are working under them.
Open your lips, ask God to help you serve Him with all your talents.
If Jesus helps you, royals, princes, kings, queens will discover your talent.
(Amen.)
Open your lips and ask God, “Help me to serve You with all my talents”.
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Help me to serve You with all my talents, time, money and labour of love – help me, Lord!
In Jesus Christ’s name, we pray.
(Amen.)
I cannot hear you.
Lord, make it happen!
(Amen.)
Make it happen!
There are many talented ones but their talent seems to be dormant.
No one, no king, no queen, no people call for it.
Lord, make it happen!
(Amen.)
You are gifted; the gifts are dormant.
You need revelation.
(Amen.)
You need what?
(Revelation.)
Meditation brings revelation.
Say it.
(Meditation brings revelation.)
I can't hear you.
Begin to meditate on the Word.
Begin to meditate on the Word – without stopping; without ceasing.
Begin to meditate on the Word – turn it over and over and over in your heart.
Meditation brings revelation.
Lord, make it happen!
(Amen.)
You know – when your talent and gift is honoured, joy comes.
Every God's general in the Bible - their talent was revealed to the king and queen.
Lord, make it happen, in the name of Jesus!
(Amen.)
Make it happen, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips right now and begin to confess your freedom.
Make it happen, Lord!
Make it happen!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Reveal my talent and gift.
Usher me to the kings and people that need me.
Make it happen!
Begin to break the chain – any chain that is holding you, your talent and gift; break it!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In the name of Jesus Christ.
(Amen.)
Yes.
This is an area the Lord said I should begin to touch before the new year.
You need to discover yourself.
(Amen.)
There are many kings, queens, people that need you but there is a chain, barrier between you and them.
Tell your neighbour: "There are many kings, queens, people that need you but there is a barrier".
I can't hear you.
But you keep praying for money and prosperity.
What kind of prosperity is that when there is a barrier?
What you need is more than prosperity and money.
There is a barrier between you and people who need you, your services, gift and talent.
There is a barrier.
The barrier is simply the wall between you and God -
a relationship must be established between you.
There is no one without gift and talent – you are created with your talent and gift.
These gifts and talents will usher you to the kings, nations and queens.
Today, the opposite is the case.
Talented people have now turned to beggars.
Whatever barrier between you, begin to break that barrier right now!
Open your lips and break the barrier!
Break the barrier!
Overflow Congregation
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In Jesus Christ’s name, we pray.
(Amen.)